question_data = [
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "Super Mario Bros. was released in 1990.", "correct_answer": "False",
         "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "The Ace Attorney trilogy was suppose to end with 'Phoenix Wright: Ace Attorney &minus; Trials "
                     "and Tribulations' as its final game.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "'Metal Gear Solid 3: Snake Eater' takes place on Shadow Moses Island.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "Metal Gear Solid V: The Phantom Pain runs on the Fox Engine.", "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "In World of Warcraft lore, Thrall is the original wielder of 'Doomhammer'.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "The Sniper's SMG in Team Fortress 2, was originally intended to be the Scout's primary weapon.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "TF2: The Medic will be credited for an assist if he heals a Spy that successfully saps a building.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "In the game '&quot;'Subnautica';, a 'Cave Crawler' will attack you.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "In Rocket League, you can play Basketball.", "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "In the video game 'Transistor', 'Red'; is the name of the main character.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "In '&quot;'League of Legends', there exists four different types of Dragon.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "'Return to Castle Wolfenstein'; was the only game of the Wolfenstein series where you don't play as William 'B.J.' Blazkowicz.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "Hidden in the files for 'Mario Kart Arcade GP' is a picture of the Beslan school hostage crisis.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "The scrapped Sonic the Hedgehog 2 level 'Hidden Palace Zone' was later reused in the iOS port of the game. ",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "In 'Resident Evil', only Chris has access to the grenade launcher.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]
